( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(شاهد على www.kissasia.co، .be، .org، .net، .id، .xyz)
You're awake?
هل أنت مستيقظ؟
Want to sit up?
هل تريد أن تجلس منتصباً؟
Where's my brother?
أين أخي؟
Get some rest.
خذ قسطاً من الراحة.
I'll go
سأذهب
tell the doctor you're awake.
أخبر الطبيب أنك مستيقظ.
My brother...
أخي...
Siyuan came to see me yesterday.
جاء سيوان لزيارتي أمس.
What?
ماذا؟
Do you regret saying all those awful things to me?
هل تندم على قول كل تلك الأشياء الفظيعة لي؟
Even if you cry your eyes out apologizing,
حتى لو بكيت بحرقة وأنت تعتذر،
I won't come back.
لن أعود.
You're overthinking.
أنت تبالغ في التفكير.
I'm not going to cry.
لن أبكي.
But I do want to apologize.
لكنني أريد أن أعتذر.
There won't be a next time.
لن يكون هناك مرة أخرى.
Then you should be willing to do me a favor, right?
إذن يجب أن تكون مستعداً لفعل معروف لي، أليس كذلك؟
That explains everything.
هذا يفسر كل شيء.
Xia Shang killed Li Xiang.
قتل شيا شانغ لي شيانغ.
Xia Shang probably found out
ربما اكتشف شيا شانغ الأمر
I hid the fact that Nongyu was collecting fragments
أخفيت حقيقة أن نونغيو كان يجمع الشظايا
and now thinks I betrayed the bureau.
والآن يعتقد أنني خنت المكتب.
So she wants to get rid of me
لذا فهي تريد التخلص مني
and the people around me.
والناس من حولي.
I'll take these fake fragments
سآخذ هذه الشظايا المزيفة
to Xia Shang.
إلى شيا شانغ.
Once she gets them,
بمجرد حصولها عليهما،
she'll definitely have the tech department
سيكون لديها بالتأكيد قسم التكنولوجيا
verify them.
تحقق منها.
Figure out a way
إيجاد طريقة
to switch the inspection report.
لتغيير تقرير الفحص.
You think giving her that
هل تعتقد أن إعطاءها ذلك سيفيدها؟
will make her let everyone go?
هل سيجعلها ذلك تسمح للجميع بالرحيل؟
I don't have long to live anyway.
على أي حال، ليس لدي الكثير لأعيشه.
So I'll offer myself
لذا سأعرض نفسي
in exchange for a deal with Xia Shang
في مقابل صفقة مع شيا شانغ
to protect Nongyu,
لحماية نونغيو،
you,
أنت،
and everyone else around me.
وكل من حولي.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I won't let you help me for nothing.
لن أدعك تساعدني مجاناً.
From today on,
ابتداءً من اليوم،
you don't have to work for the Special Administration Bureau anymore.
لم يعد عليك العمل لدى مكتب الإدارة الخاصة.
I've also made arrangements
لقد قمت أيضاً بالترتيبات اللازمة
on the matchmaking for you.
نحن نقوم بالتوفيق بينكما.
Wu Siyuan,
وو سيوان,
are you giving your last words?
هل ستلقي كلماتك الأخيرة؟
If you can,
إن أمكنك ذلك،
please take care of Nongyu for me.
أرجو أن تعتني بنونغيو من أجلي.
Siyuan
سيوان
asked me to give this to you.
طلب مني أن أعطيك هذا.
Wu Nongyu,
وو نونجيو,
you must look really ugly crying right now.
لا بد أنكِ تبدين قبيحة جداً وأنتِ تبكين الآن.
Once you've cried enough,
بعد أن تبكي بما فيه الكفاية،
don't cry anymore.
لا تبكي بعد الآن.
Li Xiang is gone.
لقد رحل لي شيانغ.
And I didn't have much time left anyway.
وعلى أي حال، لم يكن لدي الكثير من الوقت المتبقي.
Better than fading away in a hospital,
أفضل من الموت في المستشفى،
stuck with tubes,
عالقون بالأنابيب،
dying like this,
الموت بهذه الطريقة،
at least feels cool.
على الأقل يبدو الأمر رائعاً.
It's just that I'll have to trouble you
الأمر فقط أنني سأضطر إلى إزعاجك
to arrange a joint burial for Li Xiang and me.
لترتيب دفن مشترك لي ولي شيانغ.
Say,
يقول،
[sweet]
[حلو]
I never got the chance to tell you.
لم تتح لي الفرصة لأخبرك.
We were seriously together for quite a while.
لقد كنا على علاقة جدية لفترة طويلة.
We were happy.
كنا سعداء.
I have no regrets.
لا أشعر بأي ندم.
Also,
أيضًا،
the compensation I promised Xie Xinxu
التعويض الذي وعدت به شي شينشو
has been given.
تم تقديمها.
Xia Shang agreed not to touch him again.
وافق شيا شانغ على عدم لمسه مرة أخرى.
Does that
هل هذا صحيح؟
make me his lifesaver?
هل تجعلني أنقذ حياته؟
Even though I didn't do things the way you wanted,
رغم أنني لم أفعل الأشياء بالطريقة التي أردتها،
don't scold me.
لا توبخني.
Remember this.
تذكر هذا.
If you're still going after those fragments,
إذا كنت لا تزال تسعى وراء تلك الأجزاء،
keep a low profile.
حافظ على هدوئك.
Don't rush in and throw your life away trying to avenge me.
لا تتسرع وتضيع حياتك في محاولة للانتقام لي.
Your most important mission
مهمتك الأهم
is to gather all the fragments
الهدف هو جمع كل الأجزاء
and make the Special Administration Bureau lose its reason to exist.
وجعل مكتب الإدارة الخاصة يفقد سبب وجوده.
That's the smart way to take revenge.
هذه هي الطريقة الذكية للانتقام.
Last but not least,
أخيراً وليس آخراً،
you must live well.
يجب أن تعيش حياة طيبة.
Understood?
مفهوم؟
Don't come crying at our graves for no reason.
لا تأتِ باكياً إلى قبورنا بلا سبب.
You'll interrupt Li Xiang and me.
ستقاطعني أنا ولي شيانغ.
Our deal is off.
لقد انتهى اتفاقنا.
I'll find fragments on my own.
سأجد الشظايا بنفسي.
No need to contact me anymore.
لا داعي للاتصال بي بعد الآن.
I've packed my things.
لقد حزمت أمتعتي.
A courier will pick them up tomorrow.
سيقوم مندوب التوصيل باستلامها غداً.
Even though the current system says
على الرغم من أن النظام الحالي يقول
a Yin and a Ren can't divorce,
لا يمكن أن ين ورين أن ينفصلا،
we never formed a pact anyway.
لم نعقد اتفاقاً على أي حال.
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدًا،
we'll live our own lives.
سنعيش حياتنا كما نريد.
If you meet a Yin you want to form a pact with in the future,
إذا صادفت شخصًا من نوع يين وترغب في عقد اتفاق معه في المستقبل،
we'll figure something out.
سنجد حلاً.
I'll cooperate with you.
سأتعاون معك.
So you think of finding another Ren too?
هل تفكر في العثور على رين آخر أيضاً؟
Who is it?
من هذا؟
Lin Juan?
لين جوان؟
Don't forget.
لا تنسى.
I'm the sister of someone suspected of killing your parents.
أنا أخت شخص يُشتبه في قتله لوالديك.
Is it really appropriate for you to keep being with me like this?
هل من المناسب حقاً أن تستمر في البقاء معي على هذا النحو؟
I know you're hurting.
أعلم أنك تتألم.
But Wu Siyuan can't come back.
لكن وو سييوان لا يستطيع العودة.
Everything is over.
انتهى كل شيء.
Let's just go back
لنعد إلى الوراء
to our lives before,
إلى حياتنا السابقة،
please.
لو سمحت.
But every time I see you,
لكن في كل مرة أراك فيها،
it reminds me of my brother's death.
يذكرني ذلك بوفاة أخي.
I know
أنا أعرف
he took his own life.
انتحر.
It's not that you didn't save him.
ليس الأمر أنك لم تنقذه.
My mind is a mess right now.
عقلي مشوش تماماً الآن.
I can't pretend like nothing happened
لا أستطيع التظاهر وكأن شيئاً لم يحدث
the way you can.
بالطريقة التي تستطيعها.
We should stop being tangled up with each other.
يجب أن نتوقف عن التورط مع بعضنا البعض.
I forgot to tell you.
نسيت أن أخبرك.
I changed the lock.
لقد غيرت القفل.
The moment you chose Wu Siyuan,
في اللحظة التي اخترت فيها وو سيوان،
I was ready to make up my mind and let you go.
كنتُ على استعداد لاتخاذ قراري والسماح لك بالرحيل.
But my dragon suddenly appeared and saved you.
لكن تنيني ظهر فجأة وأنقذك.
Do you know what that means?
هل تعرف ماذا يعني ذلك؟
Wu Siyuan used the virus in my body
استخدم وو سييوان الفيروس الموجود في جسدي
as a moving chip
كشريحة متحركة
to connect my consciousness with the dragon's.
لربط وعيي بوعي التنين.
It suddenly appeared to save you.
لقد ظهر فجأة لينقذك.
That means
هذا يعني
no matter how much I try to give up on you,
مهما حاولت التخلي عنك،
it's useless.
انها غير مجدية.
Because my heart
لأن قلبي
already chose you.
لقد اخترتك بالفعل.
But I just thought about it.
لكنني فكرت في الأمر للتو.
As the sister of the person suspected of killing my parents,
بصفتي شقيقة الشخص المشتبه به في قتل والديّ،
we really aren't suited to that kind of relationship anymore.
لم نعد مناسبين حقاً لهذا النوع من العلاقات.
I don't want to talk about this.
لا أريد التحدث عن هذا.
It doesn't matter if you don't choose me.
لا يهم إن لم تختارني.
What matters is that I chose you.
المهم أنني اخترتك.
Until we find out the truth,
إلى أن نكتشف الحقيقة،
you're staying by my side
ستبقى بجانبي
as a hostage.
كرهينة.
Aren't you afraid I'll hate you?
ألا تخشى أن أكرهك؟
If love
إذا كان الحب
can't tie us together,
لا يمكن لأحد أن يربطنا ببعضنا البعض،
then hate will.
ثم ستسود الكراهية.
I can live with that.
أستطيع التعايش مع ذلك.
♪You smell like something strange♪
رائحتك غريبة!
♪Like wood♪
♪مثل الخشب♪
♪Like wine♪
♪مثل النبيذ♪
♪Like the fading rain♪
♪مثل المطر المتلاشي♪
♪It's not a problem I can fix♪
♪ليست مشكلة أستطيع حلها♪
♪Maybe I'm just meant to be your toy♪
♪ربما أنا مجرد لعبة بالنسبة لك♪